<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Work on Mesh Studio</title>
    <link>http://meshstudio.io/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Work on Mesh Studio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 15:35:36 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://meshstudio.io/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Leveling Up Health Savings Accounts</title>
      <link>http://meshstudio.io/work/lively/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 15:35:36 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://meshstudio.io/work/lively/</guid>
      <description>Lively is a software company that helps employers offer a modern Health Savings Account (HSA) to their employees. Their product streamlines the process of setting-up an HSA and offers a convenient dashboard to manage and administer the benefit. Lively also helps employees take full advantage of their HSA by allowing them to invest the money that they contribute into the account.
“Our goal is to facilitate and optimize how individuals save for healthcare expenses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August Mobile SDKs</title>
      <link>http://meshstudio.io/work/august/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 12:21:35 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://meshstudio.io/work/august/</guid>
      <description>August Home is the brainchild of famed industrial designer Yves Behar and Jason Johnson. Founded in 2013, the company designs and manufactures beautiful, connected home security products. August’s product lineup has grown to include connected locks, doorbells, and cameras.
The company had raised over $70MM from-top tier venture capitalists like Maveron and Bessemer Venture Partners and was acquired by Assa Abloy in October of 2017.
Problem August’s connected products are controlled with a smartphone through a mix of Bluetooth and WiFi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Security, Cloud Delivered</title>
      <link>http://meshstudio.io/work/otto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://meshstudio.io/work/otto/</guid>
      <description>Founded in 2014 by serial entrepreneur Sam Jadallah, Otto manufactures the future of ‘smart locks.’ Sam saw an opportunity to redefine home access and build a category-defining product. He felt that “a digital locking system was necessary to replace the antiquated and shockingly insecure physical key system of today.”
To power this smart lock, Otto needed to build multiple sophisticated cloud services. These services would be responsible for coordinating interactions between the locks, users, and their smartphones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Staples Easy Again</title>
      <link>http://meshstudio.io/work/staples/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://meshstudio.io/work/staples/</guid>
      <description>Staples is known as the office supply superstore, with retail locations throughout North America. Founded in 1986, Staples has grown from its humble beginnings to to over 1,500 stores. The company is publicly listed and included in the Fortune 500.
Despite being known for their extensive network of brick and mortar retail locations, over 60% of Staple’s annual revenue comes from its direct business-to-business (B2B) relationships.
The Problem In the summer of 2016, these direct customer relationships were being threatened by digital native retailers, the biggest being Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>