<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cloud on Mesh Studio</title>
    <link>https://meshstudio.io/tags/cloud/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cloud on Mesh Studio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://meshstudio.io/tags/cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Guide to Static Hosting with AWS</title>
      <link>https://meshstudio.io/blog/2019-06-29-static-hosting-with-aws/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meshstudio.io/blog/2019-06-29-static-hosting-with-aws/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Guide to Static Hosting with AWS At Mesh, we host a large number of static websites for ourselves and our customers. As a result, we’ve experimented with a number of different hosting technologies and platforms over the years. We’ve found that static hosting with AWS Simple Storage Service (S3) turns out to be a fantastic option.
In this guide, I’ll demonstrate how you can deploy a static site on AWS, complete with a custom domain, HTTPS, and lighting fast content delivery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 6 IoT Technology Choices</title>
      <link>https://meshstudio.io/blog/2018-05-22-six-iot-technology-choices/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meshstudio.io/blog/2018-05-22-six-iot-technology-choices/</guid>
      <description>6 Technology Choices To Consider When Shipping IoT Products Over the past year, we&amp;rsquo;ve worked on several high profiles IoT projects. Throughout this process, we have become acutely aware of the technical challenges that software teams will face when it comes to the shipping production grade connected devices.
Regardless of form factor, most IoT products will share a standard set of fundamental technical requirements. In this post, we enumerate several of these requirements and frame them as questions that technical leaders should be asking themselves at the onset of any IoT project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lock Down Your AWS Security With 5 Easy Steps</title>
      <link>https://meshstudio.io/blog/2018-03-29-locking-down-your-aws-in-5-steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meshstudio.io/blog/2018-03-29-locking-down-your-aws-in-5-steps/</guid>
      <description>Lock Down Your AWS Security With 5 Easy Steps For the practically paranoid, improving the security of your AWS infrastructure should be an ever-changing goal to strive towards. Large organizations understand this reality. That’s why they employ entire teams that are dedicated to continually reviewing and auditing their cloud security infrastructure.
For us startups, however, we’re focused on trying to run our company; this security stuff is just another thing to think about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>API Strategy for an Insurance Giant</title>
      <link>https://meshstudio.io/work/symetra/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meshstudio.io/work/symetra/</guid>
      <description>Founded in 1957 as a subsidiary of Safeco Insurance, Symetra Financial Corporation offers a suite of insurance, benefit, and retirement products to consumers in the United States. Through a nationwide network of financial institutions, broker-dealers, independent agents, advisors, and benefits consultants, the company serves over 2 million customers and has over $42 billion in assets under management.
As of February 2016 Symetra is wholly owned subsidiary of Sumitomo Life in Japan and is headquartered in Bellevue, Washington.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>