<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aws on Mesh Studio</title>
    <link>https://meshstudio.io/tags/aws/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Aws on Mesh Studio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://meshstudio.io/tags/aws/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Guide to Static Hosting with AWS</title>
      <link>https://meshstudio.io/blog/2019-06-29-static-hosting-with-aws/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meshstudio.io/blog/2019-06-29-static-hosting-with-aws/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Guide to Static Hosting with AWS At Mesh, we host a large number of static websites for ourselves and our customers. As a result, we’ve experimented with a number of different hosting technologies and platforms over the years. We’ve found that static hosting with AWS Simple Storage Service (S3) turns out to be a fantastic option.
In this guide, I’ll demonstrate how you can deploy a static site on AWS, complete with a custom domain, HTTPS, and lighting fast content delivery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Community at Drivers Club</title>
      <link>https://meshstudio.io/work/drivers-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 15:35:36 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meshstudio.io/work/drivers-club/</guid>
      <description>Drivers Club is a passion project of Doug Perry’s. As a car enthusiasts, he envisioned a community of like-minded individuals where members are offered a full range of services including collection management, curated events, a private lounge and automobile storage — all in a modern, climate controlled, secure, and convenient location.
The first location will be opening this summer in Redmond, WA and a reciprocal club in Scottsdale, AZ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lock Down Your AWS Security With 5 Easy Steps</title>
      <link>https://meshstudio.io/blog/2018-03-29-locking-down-your-aws-in-5-steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meshstudio.io/blog/2018-03-29-locking-down-your-aws-in-5-steps/</guid>
      <description>Lock Down Your AWS Security With 5 Easy Steps For the practically paranoid, improving the security of your AWS infrastructure should be an ever-changing goal to strive towards. Large organizations understand this reality. That’s why they employ entire teams that are dedicated to continually reviewing and auditing their cloud security infrastructure.
For us startups, however, we’re focused on trying to run our company; this security stuff is just another thing to think about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Security, Cloud Delivered</title>
      <link>https://meshstudio.io/work/otto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meshstudio.io/work/otto/</guid>
      <description>Founded in 2014 by serial entrepreneur Sam Jadallah, Otto manufactures the future of ‘smart locks.’ Sam saw an opportunity to redefine home access and build a category-defining product. He felt that “a digital locking system was necessary to replace the antiquated and shockingly insecure physical key system of today.”
To power this smart lock, Otto needed to build multiple sophisticated cloud services. These services would be responsible for coordinating interactions between the locks, users, and their smartphones.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>